<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:snf="http://www.smartnews.be/snf" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><title>VICE US</title><description>RSS feed for https://www.vice.com/en</description><link>https://www.vice.com/en%3Flocale%3Den_us</link><atom:link href="https://www.vice.com/en/rss?locale=en_us" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><language>en</language><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:18:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[The Best Dumb Stuff to Buy With Your Tax Refund Money]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/xgwp7k/what-to-do-with-tax-refund-money-buy-dumb-stuff</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:18:33 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[Now that you’re rich, it’s time to get a nacho cheese dispenser, a massage chair, and a famous drum machine.]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Man, I love getting free money. There&#x2019;s nothing I look forward to more each year than when that beautiful IRS-stamped envelope arrives in my mailbox, and I can feel, even if just for five minutes, like a goddamn Jeff Bezos (albeit one who lives in a Chicago three-flat apartment with a broken dishw</p> <div class="article__embed article__embed--vice" data-related-article="true" data-children-count="0"><iframe src="https://www.vice.com/en_us/embed/article/xgd3n3/embed" frameborder="0" style="border:0px none;margin:0px" allowfullscreen></iframe></div> <p>asher and downstairs neighbors who definitely smoke cigarettes inside). That&#x2019;s right&#x2014;I&#x2019;m talkin&#x2019; about tax refund season, baby!</p> <p>And before you go thinking that I&#x2019;m a dumbass because I said the money is free and not <i>[Googles &#x201C;what is a tax refund&#x201D;]</i> what happens when you pay more than you owe or qualify for a refundable credit, let&#x2019;s just slow down for a minute. We&#x2019;re all in the same boat here: The companies we work for steal our time through the act of wage labor, generating surplus value for their own purposes; meanwhile, the government forces us to write them a check for services nobody <i>really</i> understands or agrees with&#x2026; and then Uncle Sam distracts us from all of it by sending us a few bucks and saying, &#x201C;Sorry, we &#x2018;accidentally&#x2019; stole too much, so go buy a new TV!&#x201D; (Crazy that they seem to prefer this to, I don&#x2019;t know, just taking the right amount of money in the first place?) In any case, as far as I&#x2019;m concerned, this process is <strike>cause enough for revolution</strike> absolutely awesome. We built this country, so let&#x2019;s just make the most of it by wasting our tax refund money and getting back into the red as quickly as humanly possible.</p> <p>On that note, here are some of the awesomest, silliest, dumbest things you could possibly do with your tax refund money.</p> <h2>Yes, yo cheese machine</h2> <p>Inviting me over to watch the Big Game (aka literally any baseball game)? Don&#x2019;t even bother if you don&#x2019;t have a real nacho cheese dispenser fired up with that yellow sludge we all love. Don&#x2019;t forget the jalape&#xF1;os&#x2014;you can afford &#x2018;em now, so there&#x2019;s no excuse. And you&#x2019;d <i>better</i> serve it all in a stadium-style plastic nacho tray, or I won&#x2019;t be coming back for the All-Star Game.</p> <h2>Become the king of beats you already think you are</h2> <p>Just getting into making beats? Trying to save your failing SoundCloud career with one last ditch effort for a Billboard hit before you decide to accept that manager job (and your fate) at Arby&#x2019;s? Well, why not get a Roland TR-08, Roland&#x2019;s Boutique Series update of the TR-808, which is probably the most famous drum machine ever made? If you know in your heart that your songs are as good as those by 808 greats like Run-DMC, Public Enemy, Kanye West, Outkast, New Order, and Beyonc&#xE9;, it&#x2019;s time to prove it.</p> <h2>Chill out like you&#x2019;re rich (which you were, before you bought this)</h2> <p>Want to watch <i>Real Housewives</i> (or <i>The Sopranos</i> again) in style, instead of on your current couch, which absolutely annihilates your back when you binge for more than an hour? Now that you&#x2019;ve finally got some money (that you already earned a year ago), get an Eames chair replica.</p> <h2>Soothe your ADHD</h2> <p>This ferrite putty is actually extremely fun to play with&#x2014;it&#x2019;s basically Silly Putty but made of magnets. I play with this every time I&#x2019;m on a video call (or in therapy or when my fianc&#xE9;e is telling me something important, or&#x2026;.)</p> <h2>You don&#x2019;t have to travel for great food anymore</h2> <p>Sure, you&#x2019;re in the 1% now, but that doesn&#x2019;t mean you need to blow all your hard-earned cash traveling around the U.S. to sample its finest cuisine. Hot tip: If you want to travel somewhere to dine, just order the food on Goldbelly and eat it on your couch while watching <i>Criminal Minds</i>. Dying to get to Nashville to finally try chef Sean Brock&#x2019;s JoyBurger? Or sweating at the mere thought of visiting Arizona just to eat Chris Bianco&#x2019;s famous wood-fired pizza? Want to have Guy Fieri&#x2019;s nachos in your house? Smash that &#x201C;order&#x201D; button, bro!</p> <h2>Star in your own Hot Ones episode</h2> <p>Sure, you <i>do</i> have to be rich and famous to get featured in a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLAzrgbu8gEMIIK3r4Se1dOZWSZzUSadfZ" target="_blank">Hot Ones</a> episode, but if you want to enjoy the experience of tasting 10 mouth-numbing hot sauces and then having an existential episode, just shell out for a real, authentic Hot Ones sauce lineup. Get this pack of sauces from season 22 and join the ranks of Doja Cat, Bobby Flay, Cardi B, and *NSYNC in blowing your taste buds out (deliciously).</p> <h2>Nurture your cultured side</h2> <p>Nothing says luxury like a big, ol&#x2019; Blu-ray box set that you don&#x2019;t need. Now that you&#x2019;re retired, spend your time going through The Criterion Collection&#x2019;s, uh, collection of early Jackie Chan films; or buy their Ingmar Bergman box set that includes 39 of his films (even though you&#x2019;ll only watch <i>Persona</i> and the wrong version of <i>Fanny and Alexander</i>). If you&#x2019;re a <i>Twin Peaks</i> fan, finally peep the show the way David Lynch intended: in high quality and not on a compressed, laggy streaming service!</p> <h2>Time for a massage chair</h2> <p>If you&#x2019;re like me, you&#x2019;ve always told yourself (and your partner) that you were absolutely, 100% going to buy a massage chair when you had the space. But now, you&#x2019;re wealthy beyond your wildest dreams and anything is possible&#x2026; so cop that bad boy right now.</p> <h2>Rock out with your&#x2026; wallet empty</h2> <p>Fashion yourself a troubadour? No better time to upgrade your rig for playing Incubus and Smashing Pumpkins covers than when you have some disposable income. Thus, the beautiful, new, top-of-the-line Taylor acoustic guitar you&#x2019;ve always dreamed of is finally on the table.</p> <h2>You&#x2019;re the grillmaster, now</h2> <p>Love pancakes? Time to do some <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ykELuxlghAQ" target="_blank">Johnny Cakes cosplay</a> and become a sexy grill man at your own diner (i.e. your kitchen) by copping a pancake batter dispenser.</p> <h2>Get fancy with your wine</h2> <p>Nothing says &#x201C;I had an extra $40&#x201D; like a real porron, aka a Spanish wine pitcher with a small spout that lets you pour wine into your mouth from above without spilling. This is how rich people party.</p> <h2>A Margaritaville-branded frozen concoction maker, obviously</h2> <p>Jimmy Buffet might be gone (RIP), but keep his dream alive with a real, branded Margaritaville &#x201C;frozen concoction maker.&#x201D; Because, like, why <i>wouldn&#x2019;t</i> you want to make killer frozen <strike>margaritas</strike> concoctions at your leisure?</p> <h2>Chill out</h2> <p>It might sound counterintuitive because of how goddamn expensive it is to heat an apartment these days, but rich people absolutely love being cold. Like, they make themselves cold on purpose, because it&#x2019;s apparently good for your body and circulatory system. Honor your newfound social status by investing in an insulated cold barrel for ice therapy.</p> <p>Send me a postcard from Margaritaville, please!</p> <hr> <p><i>The Rec Room staff independently selected all of the stuff featured in this story.</i></p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">xgwp7k</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/65c2a7997761a980a5fb3e17/lede/1707256225256-taxrefund1.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Adam Rothbarth</dc:creator><dc:creator>HP </dc:creator><category>shopping-style</category><category>taxes</category><category>tax refund</category><category>Nachos</category><category>rich</category><category>wealthy</category><category>1%er</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Best Neutral Sneakers (for Running, Partying, and Looking Put Together)]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/bvmpza/best-neutral-sneakers</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[Match-everything neutral sneakers are a wardrobe essential, especially these classics from Hoka, Adidas, Vans, and Nike.]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Expanding your closet&#x2019;s color palette is fun, but there&#x2019;s something to be said (aesthetically <i>and</i> financially) about investing in pieces that match all of your garb. (Bright pink <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgdk73/best-crocs" target="_blank">platform Crocs</a> can only pair well with so much, with or without <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/4axxeg/crocs-charms-spoilers" target="_blank">Croc-adjacent truck nuts</a>.) It&#x2019;s no secret that the bedrock of even the wildest wardrobes is ultimately a suite of sensible, neutral colorways&#x2014;think white, beige, tan, gray, black, brown, and navy. If you&#x2019;re a regular around these parts, you know that <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/topic/shopping-style" target="_blank">we&#x2019;re up for just about anything</a> when it comes to building our wardrobes, but even we can appreciate a good neutral, and that goes double when we&#x2019;re shopping for sneakers.</p> <div class="article__embed article__embed--vice" data-related-article="true" data-children-count="0"><iframe src="https://www.vice.com/en_us/embed/article/epza8k/embed" frameborder="0" style="border:0px none;margin:0px" allowfullscreen></iframe></div> <p>Match-everything sneakers are a wardrobe essential, which is why we compiled a list of the best neutral sneakers to buy, so you can pick up any of these kicks and know you&#x2019;ll be able to pair them with your <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5vvxj/best-bolo-ties" target="_blank">bolo tie</a>,<a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/ake7kb/corn-shirt" target="_blank">corn shirt</a>, and sweater for <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/88qdgv/best-fall-sweaters-for-men" target="_blank">cozy bois</a>. Whether you need a versatile athletic shoe or something a bit more pared-down for brunch with the folks, we found all the options you need to build your look from the bottom up&#x2014;literally.</p> <h2>Converse Chuck 70 Vintage Canvas</h2> <p>You may not see Chucks on the court anymore, but you can spot them pretty much everywhere else. Converse&#x2019;s iconic canvas shoe adds a smidge of vintage character to any and all fits&#x2014;whether you&#x2019;re wearing gorpcore streetwear or business casual slacks&#x2014;while its OrthoLite interior provides much-needed modern comfort.</p> <h2>Reebok Club C 85 Vintage Shoes</h2> <p>If you&#x2019;ve stomped around any hip cities lately, chances are you&#x2019;ve seen the Reebok Club C 85 Vintage one too many times. We&#x2019;re also certifying this 80s shoe as a classic for its sleek, premium white leather and retro silhouette. Plus, the little British flag detailing along the side provides a tiny dose of European style.</p> <h2>Hoka Clifton 9</h2> <p>If you don&#x2019;t already know how we feel about <a href="https://www.hoka.com/" target="_blank">Hoka</a>, you&#x2019;ve been living under a rock. Besides being <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjkjk7/hoka-clifton-8-review" target="_blank">a slappin&#x2019; running shoe</a> ever since its first model was introduced in 2014, this newer iteration comes in an array of muted colors that pair well with trousers or add a touch of athleisure to what would otherwise be a fairly basic business casual fit. We love them in classic white and creamy eggnog, which only drives home the fact that most Hoka models look (and feel) like marshmallows for your feet. The Clifton has neutral stability, balanced cushioning, breathable mesh, and the option to choose various widths, in case you need a wider toe-box.</p> <h2>New Balance 990v4 Core</h2> <p><a href="https://www.newbalance.com/" target="_blank">New Balance</a> may be the go-to shoe brand for dad-style disciples, but we think that a demographic that consistently suffers from sore feet and stubborn back issues knows where to find sneakers that hit the sweet spot between comfort and utility. This updated &#x201C;v4&#x201D; iteration of the New Balance signature silhouette from 1982 will impress your friends with its firm and supportive midsole without sacrificing style.</p> <h2>Nike Air Force 1</h2> <p>This retro basketball sneaker-turned-street style staple is one <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BfzsMQGqrt0" target="_blank">you don&#x2019;t need to be Nelly</a> to appreciate. Originally launched in 1982, the Air Force 1 remains one of <a href="https://www.nike.com/" target="_blank">Nike</a>&#x2019;s best sellers thanks in no small part to its simple (but still sporty) silhouette and suite of colorway options. That said, there&#x2019;s no topping monochromatic options in either all-white or all-black. While a pair of Air Force 1s is sure to receive plenty of play since either one of the aforementioned colorways will integrate with any &#x2018;fit, it&#x2019;s equally important to know when to retire your pair and move on to the next; no matter how universally appealing the Air Force 1 is, no one likes a flamb&#xE9;d pair of Forces. Keep &#x2018;em fresh.</p> <h2>Asics GEL-Lyte III</h2> <p>Retro sneaker styles are in, and this <a href="https://www.asics.com/" target="_blank">Asics</a> model designed in the early 90s fills that throwback style void for us, all while being comfy and matchy-matchy with everything you already own. Tech men may have mastered the trainers-with-jeans getup, but it&#x2019;s not the Mark Zuckerberg vibe we&#x2019;re after&#x2014;it&#x2019;s the swaggier side of normcore. This sneaker has the looks that will match everything from your <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7vy48/best-shackets-chore-coats" target="_blank">F/W2022 chore coat</a> to your <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkgzd8/instagram-shopping-wish-list" target="_blank">bootleg Cocteau Twins long sleeve</a>, and its gel-heel technology cushions the heel to help improve shock absorption for lasting comfort while walking all day long.</p> <h2>Vans Authentic</h2> <p>These are classics for a reason. Built with skateboarding roots and simple style, this <a href="https://www.vans.com/en-us/shoes-c00081/authentic-pvn0a5jmp1nu" target="_blank">Vans</a> silhouette and canvas material has remained timeless ever since it first hit the streets in 1966. Incorporating Vans&#x2019; signature rubber waffle outsole, the Authentic (originally known as the #44 Deck Shoe) manages to sit comfortably across a variety of different vibes; whether you&#x2019;re someone with a Connecticut summer house or a skater prone to hopping fences and skating in pools, this sneaker fits the bill. Our favorite neutral shade in these suckers? Gray.</p> <h2>Adidas Samba</h2> <p>You&#x2019;ve got to admire the eternal appeal of the <a href="https://www.adidas.com/us" target="_blank">Adidas</a> Samba. (We love it so much that <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/epza8k/adidas-samba" target="_blank">we wrote an entire article</a> on its well-deserved renaissance.) The timeless silhouette has a classic leather upper body, lightweight gum rubber outsole, oblong tongue, and low profile. You don&#x2019;t need to keep up with the English Premier League or justify their spot in your sneaker rotation with stories about your &#x201C;glory days&#x201D; playing club soccer back in college&#x2014;the Samba is a bona fide style icon.</p> <h2>Veja Campo</h2> <p>Like many luxury-leaning sneaker companies, <a href="https://www.nordstrom.com/s/veja-campo-sneaker-men/5147308" target="_blank">Veja</a> has its own bougie version of <a href="https://www.adidas.com/us" target="_blank">Adidas</a>&#x2019; iconic <a href="https://www.adidas.com/us/stan_smith" target="_blank">Stan Smiths</a>. In other words, you&#x2019;ll be adding the minimalist appeal of the OG tennis shoe, with the smug feeling of superiority of knowing that your kicks cost significantly more than the run-of-the-mill Stan Smith. Hey, <a href="https://www.nordstrom.com/brands/veja--11601" target="_blank">Veja</a> is a French footwear brand, so you can at least look like you automatically know <i>fashion</i>.</p> <p>Oh my god, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3HjIljJd-o0" target="_blank">shoes</a>.</p> <hr> <p><i>The Rec Room staff independently selected all of the stuff featured in this story. Want more reviews, recommendations, and red-hot deals? <a href="https://link1.vice.com/join/6qz/signup-recroom" target="_blank">Sign up for our newsletter</a>.</i></p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">bvmpza</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/634ed9808349520093dfd781/lede/1666302841053-neutral-sneakers-getty.jpeg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><dc:creator>Nicolette Accardi</dc:creator><dc:creator>Gregory Babcock</dc:creator><dc:creator>Hilary Pollack</dc:creator><category>shopping-style</category><category>Sneakers</category><category>Neutral</category><category>Evergreen</category><category>samba</category><category>Nike Air</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[17 Getaway Ideas for a Weird, Wonderful, Non-Traditional Romantic Vacation]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/4awyqm/unique-couples-vacation-airbnb-joshua-tree</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[Who needs a couples resort for Valentine's Day when you can make out in a converted bunker, dome home, or a hippie houseboat?]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#x2019;re not like most couples on Valentine&#x2019;s Day <i>[uncorks <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awyz9/shrek-anal-plug-unique-sex-toy" target="_blank">Shrek butt plug</a>],</i> which isn&#x2019;t to say you don&#x2019;t dig a classic couple&#x2019;s vacation activity, but we think you can do better than the old beachside massage package/wine tasting/hot air balloon venture (does anyone actually do that outside of Santa Fe or <i>The Bachelor</i>?? Let us know).&#xA0;</p> <div class="article__embed article__embed--vice" data-related-article="true" data-children-count="0"><iframe src="https://www.vice.com/en_us/embed/article/xgdvd7/embed" frameborder="0" style="border:0px none;margin:0px" allowfullscreen></iframe></div> <p>In fact, you know what? For your next couple&#x2019;s vacation, <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjkzpq/best-massage-candles-dripping-wax" target="_blank">leave the massages to us</a> whilst you and your hunny explore more intriguing pastures; if you must do the spa thing, why not <a href="https://www.bustle.com/articles/78427-at-the-russian-and-turkish-baths-i-was-beaten-with-oak-leaves-to-exfoliate-my-skin" target="_blank">get tenderized by oak leaves</a> together at a <a href="https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g60763-d142485-Reviews-Russian_Turkish_Baths-New_York_City_New_York.html" target="_blank">Russian and Turkish bathhouse</a>? Feel like branching out even more? Take a pilgrimage to the best <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7vp8z/unique-kitschy-hotels-in-the-us" target="_blank">kitsch roadside hotels</a> or sign up for a <a href="https://www.airbnb.co.za/experiences/658128" target="_blank">guided nudist hike</a>. We really do live in the golden era of <a href="https://www.airbnb.com/s/experiences" target="_blank">Airbnb experiences</a>, and the world is your weird, briny oyster for the slurping before tantric sex.&#xA0;</p> <p>Maybe you&#x2019;re looking to skip town with your new situationship for a bit, or trying to add some spice to the stew of your <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/wxd5jn/best-gifts-long-term-boyfriend-girlfriend-partner" target="_blank">five-year-strong relationship</a> this Valentine&#x2019;s Day; maybe you need a cozy spot for two, or four, or you and six <a href="https://www.etsy.com/listing/1093625050/long-furby-minty-and-light-blue-boi" target="_blank">long Furbies</a>. Whatever your reason for getting out of Dodge, we&#x2019;ve found a bunch of non-traditional vacations and rentals for y&#x2019;all to dip into a sudsy and swimmable Champagne glass, bone in a grotto, or make out in a veritable Bio-Dome in Joshua Tree.</p> <h2>You&#x2019;re still thinking about &#x2018;The White Lotus&#x2019;</h2> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1675440027234-screen-shot-2023-02-03-at-105952-am.png" alt="Screen Shot 2023-02-03 at 10.59.52 AM.png"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Plum Guide</div></div> <p>&#x2026; Maybe you even binged Mike White&#x2019;s award-winning season with your fellow married friends (how brave of you), and you want to <strike>put everyone&#x2019;s partnerships to the test</strike> check out Italy for yourselves. So here&#x2019;s an idea: Instigate your own toxic love squares in Taormina, Siciliy, in the same village where <strike>Christopher Moltisanti</strike> Dominic Di Grasso gets chewed out by his distant-distant cousins in the series. The whimsical estate is smack in the middle of the countryside, and just a fifteen-minute drive from the Spiaggia di Isola Bella and Spiaggia di Mazzeo beaches. Plus, it sleeps up to ten guests (very orgy-friendly).</p> <p><i><b>The Libretto; sleeps up to 10, $1,238 at <a href="https://www.plumguide.com/homes/60233/the-libretto" target="_blank">Plum Guide</a></b></i></p> <h2>Stay at a designer house in Palermo&#x2026;</h2> <div class="article__media"><a target="_blank"><img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/seKcQKTDqFGAEz830AxwKEanJCv2Quk1m-ChO0yHyM4JMHwgGs_2SeU0xxOnh8KQacflMApW2hIurfGIsANzENQQdGOAZF9uIe5ANOTzfN4gaDMgDS1n3wca3qrqSZonq4xle756LSSwUdggkA4sAxw" alt="Screen Shot 2023-02-03 at 12.11.58 PM.png"></a><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>This apartment in Palermo, Italy looks like the brainchild of Serge Gainsbourg and a well-read, brooding Italian widower. It was designed by the artist and designer Giuseppe Amato in the iconic <i>Politeama Libert&#xE0;</i> district, which is at the heart of Palermo, and it&#x2019;s complete with an elevator and three bedrooms&#x2014;to say nothing of the bedframes, which will give you the ability to have sex in cursive.</p> <p><i><b>Liberty Library; sleeps up to 6, $194/night at <a href="https://airbnb.pvxt.net/LPAPya" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>&#x2026; Or this home on the &quot;American Riviera</h2> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/Q_mLj_AqkO9W9KGSjvyW3FHK2qKpyI6t6sRY1-DO_cVlKnTonvWICffe4Pgp6VatdeiiFxqiwfu7rmZLLk7mymioy5ZrvW8FyxJWfF8duAGX6XSVotW9dFncy6lRijNf9R8z7ehp33T5cJDI6nQXeyw" alt="Screen Shot 2023-02-03 at 12.40.31 PM.png"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>Don&#x2019;t have time to go all the way to Italy? Try heading to Santa Barbara, California, a.k.a. the &#x201C;<a href="https://www.travelchannel.com/destinations/us/ca/photos/santa-barbara-the-american-riviera" target="_blank">American Riviera</a>.&#x201D; The city is beloved for its Mediterranean climate, pristine beaches, and great wine, and this home overlooks all of the downtown area. Grill something tender on the outdoor BBQ, and settle in for a night making out on the (linen!!) bedding.</p> <p><i><b>Riviera Studio; sleeps up to 2, $314/night at <a href="https://airbnb.pvxt.net/jWxWGn" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>All aboard the love boat&#xA0;</h2> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1635862088024-69e88ceeoriginal.jpeg" alt="69e88cee_original.jpeg"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>The houseboats of Sausalito, California have a long history as one of the more unique bohemian communities in the state; they were even featured in an <a href="https://youtu.be/BW5attplYjA" target="_blank">Agn&#xE8;s Varda&#x2019;s</a> documentary on the area, and continue to entice travelers with their <i>Waterworld-</i>romantic feel. This floating guest cottage is the last boat of its kind on the northward leg of the dock, and has beautiful views of Mount Tamalpais.&#xA0;</p> <p><i><b>Floating Guest Cottage; sleeps up to 4, $256/night at <a href="https://airbnb.pvxt.net/e4y45g" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>Attend elf school together in Iceland</h2> <p><i>[Chortles in Hulduf&#xF3;lk.] </i>Honestly, heading to Reykjav&#xED;k for a long-weekend jaunt if you live on the East Coast isn&#x2019;t that crazy or (comparatively) expensive if you want to feel like you&#x2019;re on another planet; you can easily get a round-trip flight, which is way cheaper than <a href="https://www.findingtheuniverse.com/visit-space-as-a-tourist/#:~:text=You%20can%20buy%20tickets%20for,previous%20space%20travellers%20have%20paid." target="_blank">visiting space with Virgin Galactic</a>. We also have an entire <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/epnnxj/iceland-travel-guide-covid-vaccine" target="_blank">guide of what to do in Iceland</a>, from staying at the best Airbnbs, like this<a href="https://airbnb.pvxt.net/Aoxo1R" target="_blank"> Reykjavik cabin</a> sitting right under the Northern Lights&#x2026;</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1635818270357-northern-lights.jpeg" alt="northern lights.jpeg"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>&#x2026; to attending the <a href="https://theelfschool.com/" target="_blank">Elf School</a>, which is a real thing that exists. Sign your partner and yourself up for a crash course, and learn about the importance of elf folklore and influence on Icelandic culture. &#x201C;It felt more like a casual evening with grandpa than just a tour,&#x201D; writes one diploma-holder; &#x201C;[the] teacher Magnus [&#x2026;] made the class such a wonderful experience,&#x201D; writes another, &#x201C;Totally recommend this for anyone travelling to Iceland.&#x201D;</p> <p><i><b>Learn more about Elf School on <a href="https://www.tripadvisor.com/ShowUserReviews-g189970-d10484472-r613449014-Icelandic_Elfschool-Reykjavik_Capital_Region.html" target="_blank">Tripadvisor</a></b></i></p> <h2>Hot lovin&#x2019; in the Cold War bunker</h2> <div class="article__media"><a target="_blank"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1635806783909-9d93bb21-3423-499d-bdda-5cd76978e77d.jpeg" alt="9d93bb21-3423-499d-bdda-5cd76978e77d.jpeg"></a><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>Remember that Dean Martin song? This converted bunker is in Roswell, New Mexico, so you might just see some little green dudes when you wind down into its 186-foot deep nethers for a romantic evening with your history buff/aspiring war criminal lover. There&#x2019;s also a tour of the old Launch Control Center included.&#xA0;</p> <div class="article__media"><a target="_blank"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1635818114923-screen-shot-2021-11-01-at-95457-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2021-11-01 at 9.54.57 PM.png"></a><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p><i><b>Cold War Bunker; sleeps up to 2, $499/night at <a href="https://airbnb.pvxt.net/15n5Mg" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>You&#x2019;re the spooky A24 couple</h2> <div class="article__media"><a target="_blank"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1675452512919-screen-shot-2023-02-03-at-22742-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2023-02-03 at 2.27.42 PM.png"></a><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p><i>We know, we know</i>&#x2014;y&#x2019;all aren&#x2019;t big on Valentine&#x2019;s Day because you&#x2019;re too cool for corporate holidays, but that doesn&#x2019;t mean you can&#x2019;t seize the opportunity to rent out a converted goth silo and watch <i>The Witch </i>(one of your first date movies) again. The moody abode is situated on over a hundred acres in Litchfield, Connecticut, and is just a little over two hours from Manhattan by car. Plus, the primary restroom has an extra large soaking tub.</p> <p><i><b>Silo House; sleeps up to 4, $599/night at <a href="https://airbnb.pvxt.net/JrervQ" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>The converted Parisian abbey</h2> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1675450186884-screen-shot-2023-02-03-at-14923-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2023-02-03 at 1.49.23 PM.png"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Plum Guide</div></div> <p><a href="https://www.architecturaldigest.com/story/middle-ages-modern-medieval-design-trend" target="_blank">Contemporary medieval aesthetics</a> are so hot right now, and few places on this bulbous Earth have the ye old clout of Paris, France. This luxury apartment is situated in the city&#x2019;s Left Bank, and built on the only remaining wall of the 13th century Saint Germain-des-Pr&#xE9;s Abbey. You&#x2019;ll be nearby the Luxembourg Gardens, the Caf&#xE9; de Flore&#x2014;all the <i>rive gauche </i>classics.</p> <p><i><b>The Abbey House; sleeps up to 6, $2,657/night at <a href="https://www.plumguide.com/homes/2485/labbaye-de-saint-germain" target="_blank">Plum Guide</a></b></i></p> <h2>A Brutalist retreat in Oaxaca</h2> <div class="article__media"><a target="_blank"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1675451201379-screen-shot-2023-02-03-at-20621-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2023-02-03 at 2.06.21 PM.png"></a><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>If you&#x2019;re lover is a fan of Ricardo Bofill&#x2019;s converted 1973 <a href="https://www.archdaily.cl/cl/02-211397/the-factory-ricardo-bofill#:~:text=En%201973%20Ricardo%20Bofill%20encontr%C3%B3,sede%20del%20Taller%20de%20Arquitectura." target="_blank">factory home</a> in Spain, they&#x2019;ll fall bum over noggin for this Brutalist oasis in Oaxaca, Mexico. It&#x2019;s nestled amongst some lush greenery, has air conditioning, <i>and </i>it&#x2019;s pet-friendly. Come for a week (and stay for the month).</p> <p><i><b>Bright Oaxacan Loft; sleeps up to 2, $52/night at <a href="https://airbnb.pvxt.net/oemegg" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>Your own personal waterpark</h2> <div class="article__media"><a target="_blank"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1675451701589-screen-shot-2023-02-03-at-21421-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2023-02-03 at 2.14.21 PM.png"></a><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>Why don&#x2019;t you bring your <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/88q4ka/tiktok-viral-lovability-waterslyde-sex-toy" target="_blank">WaterSlyde</a> to this water slide oasis in the desert by Yucca Valley, California? The Joshua Tree-adjacent home has ample makeout spots in its pool&#x2014;including a hot tub hidden behind a cave&#x2014;and a large outdoor stage with a projector for watching <i>Wild at Heart.</i></p> <p><i><b>Hidden Yucca Valley Paradise; sleeps up to 8, $439/night at <a href="https://airbnb.pvxt.net/n1r1Zx" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>Joshua Tree glamping</h2> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1675452076160-screen-shot-2023-02-03-at-22058-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2023-02-03 at 2.20.58 PM.png"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p><a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/qj8wgx/what-is-glamping-best-rentals-diy" target="_blank">In the words </a>of Rec Room editor Hilary Pollack, &#x201C;Glamping is a stupid word, but a great idea.&#x201D; This private camp ground by Joshua Tree can welcome up to eight of your lovers/besties, and it&#x2019;s complete with a pool table, private backyard, hot tob, and heating and air conditioning.</p> <p><i><b>Desert Escape; sleeps up to 8, $237/night at <a href="https://airbnb.pvxt.net/6b3bQN" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>Off the grid</h2> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1707254082670-screen-shot-2024-02-06-at-31428-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2024-02-06 at 3.14.28 PM.png"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Plum Guide</div></div> <p>If you&#x2019;re trying to get out of town (and over the sea and away from society altogether), this little stone cottage in Greece will do the trick. Plus, if you&#x2019;re into the whole &#x201C;body of water overlooking significantly bigger body of water&#x201D; thing, you&#x2019;ll love the pool here.</p> <p><i><b>Mystic Mirage, sleeps 2, $339 at <a href="https://www.plumguide.com/homes/1093905/mystic-mirage?adults=2" target="_blank">Plum Guide</a></b></i></p> <h2>A literal private island</h2> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1707254182069-screen-shot-2024-02-06-at-31602-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2024-02-06 at 3.16.02 PM.png"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>Last year, Airbnb dropped a <a href="https://news.airbnb.com/discover-wes-andersons-asteroid-city-on-airbnb/?irgwc=1&amp;irclid=ytoRfvQgDxyPWIVXnHwo4xa0UkHwuQ3JIXpny40&amp;ircid=4273&amp;sharedid=vice&#x2061;=&amp;iratid=9627&amp;c=.pi73.pk4273_1331429&amp;irparam1=" target="_blank">world-spanning list of getaways</a> that feel like they&#x2019;re in Wes Anderson films. This cabin in Norway also comes with <i>[checks notes]</i> a 10,000-square-foot island. Precious indie soundtrack not included.</p> <p><i><b>Private Island in Sunny Hvaler, sleeps 8, $235 at <a href="http://airbnb.pvxt.net/KjA2jN" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>This forest retreat</h2> <div class="article__media"><a target="_blank"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1707254318507-screen-shot-2024-02-06-at-31824-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2024-02-06 at 3.18.24 PM.png"></a></div> <p>People love to talk about the wine of California, but Oregon has a ton of great wineries, as well. This place has absolutely nothing to do with wine, but we predict the selection at the wine shop you&#x2019;ll hit before heading out into the middle of nowhere to this cabin next to the Columbia River will be awesome. Plus, getting drunk might help you figure out how to pass the time.</p> <p><i><b>Hummingbird Garden, sleeps 6, $414 at <a href="https://www.plumguide.com/homes/35098/hummingbird-garden" target="_blank">Plum Guide</a></b></i></p> <h2>Feel like a spy</h2> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1707254386134-screen-shot-2024-02-06-at-31932-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2024-02-06 at 3.19.32 PM.png"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>No, Caribbean villas with this kind of view are <i>not</i> only for spies, tech geniuses, and Brad Pitt. You, too, can rent this whole home in St. Lucia&#x2014;and for a pretty decent price.</p> <p><i><b>Gorgeous Oceanfront Villa With Pool and Concierge, sleeps 8, $875 at <a href="http://airbnb.pvxt.net/xkPXk1" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <h2>King of the castle</h2> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1707254439480-screen-shot-2024-02-06-at-32025-pm.png" alt="Screen Shot 2024-02-06 at 3.20.25 PM.png"><div class="article__image-caption">Photo: Airbnb</div></div> <p>OK, picture this: You&#x2019;re in Germany, staying in a huge, 800-year-old castle. You&#x2019;re drinking some kind of unimaginably good local lager. No armies can attack you, due to the strategic location of your castle on a large vineyard on a hill and the forest surrounding it. No, it&#x2019;s not medieval times&#x2014;you&#x2019;re just renting a room in Bad H&#xF6;nningen.</p> <p><i><b>Castle in Bad H&#xF6;nningen, sleeps 2, $204 at <a href="http://airbnb.pvxt.net/Qygzyo" target="_blank">Airbnb</a></b></i></p> <p>Happy romancing, ya freaks.&#xA0;</p> <hr> <p><i>The Rec Room staff independently selected all of the stuff featured in this story. Want more reviews, recommendations, and red-hot deals? <a href="https://link1.vice.com/join/6qz/signup-recroom" target="_blank">Sign up for our newsletter</a>.</i></p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">4awyqm</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/618069dd92984e009add7544/lede/1675455481903-the-best-unique-rentals-for-valentines-day.jpeg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><dc:creator>Mary Frances "Francky" Knapp</dc:creator><dc:creator>Ian Burke</dc:creator><dc:creator>Hilary Pollack</dc:creator><category>shopping-travel</category><category>Travel</category><category>Valentine's Day</category><category>The VICE Valentine's Day Gift Guide</category><category>date ideas</category><category>Evergreen</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Daily Horoscope: February 7, 2024]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/y3w4mw/daily-horoscope-february-7-2024</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[Venus aligns with Uranus and Mars harmonizes with Neptune.]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We&#x2019;re met with a sense of genuine love and kindness, a no-nonsense type of love, as the moon and Venus meet in Capricorn at 3:12 PM.&#xA0;</p> <p>We&#x2019;re grounded enough to embrace unpredictable events as the moon and Venus (in Capricorn) connect with Uranus in Taurus at 3:19 PM and 4:25 PM, respectively. We&#x2019;re open to novelty!</p> <p>Acting on our beliefs comes easier as Mars in Capricorn harmonizes with Neptune in Pisces at 7:20 PM. Meaning-making inspires us to move forward, regardless of the unknowns.</p> <p>All times ET.</p> <p><b><a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7bwqx/your-monthly-horoscope-february-2024" target="_blank">Read your monthly horoscope for February!</a></b></p> <p><b>Stay in the cosmic loop with the VICE horoscopes newsletter. Get horoscopes straight to your inbox when you <a href="https://link1.vice.com/join/6qz/signup-horoscopes&amp;hash=cb227691f584426b4a0adeb7c0745e7f" target="_blank">sign up here!</a></b></p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280357703-1aries.png" alt="Aries glyph"></div> <h2>Aries: March 19, 2024 - April 19, 2024</h2> <p>Surprising announcements about your career or role in public could come to light as Venus in Capricorn aligns with Uranus in Taurus. You might be stepping into a new position or accepting an award! You&#x2019;re able to leave the past behind and embrace what&#x2019;s ahead, even if you&#x2019;re not certain of the details, as Mars in Capricorn also harmonizes with Neptune in Pisces today.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280387209-2taurus.png" alt="Taurus glyphs"></div> <h2>Taurus: April 19, 2024 - May 20, 2024</h2> <p>Exciting conversations about travel or furthering education could arise as Venus in Capricorn aligns with Uranus in your sign, Taurus. You&#x2019;re ready to materialize a dream, and you might surprise others with how suddenly you put things into motion as Mars in Capricorn also harmonizes with Neptune in Pisces today. You&#x2019;re confident about whatever journey lies ahead of you.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280404861-3gemini.png" alt="Gemini glyph"></div> <h2>Gemini: May 20, 2024 - June 20, 2024</h2> <p>Boundaries could be shifting and ideals about ownership may be changing in a harmonious way as Mars in Capricorn links with Neptune in Pisces. Ongoing financial deals and other negotiations might need more time or information to be wrapped up, though contracts could be voided to start over if stipulations weren&#x2019;t clearly defined.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280458930-4cancer.png" alt="Cancer glyph"></div> <h2>Cancer: June 20, 2024 - July 22, 2024</h2> <p>Spontaneous vibes enliven your relationships today as Venus in Capricorn aligns with Uranus in Taurus. Your friends or significant others could surprise you with something luxurious, romantic, or something wildly weird (but enjoyable, nonetheless)!&#xA0; A fantasy might just come true as Mars in Capricorn harmonizes with Neptune in Pisces&#x2026;or at least it could feel like it, even if it doesn&#x2019;t look how you thought it would.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280479163-5leo.png" alt="Leo glyph"></div> <h2>Leo: July 22, 2024 - August 22, 2024</h2> <p>You could be pleasantly surprised by how much you can trust the people you work with as Venus in Capricorn aligns with Uranus in Taurus. People you share responsibilities or goals with may swoop in to make your load a lot easier today, fostering respect and boosting morale.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280495172-6virgo.png" alt="Virgo glyph"></div> <h2>Virgo: August 22, 2024 - September 22, 2024</h2> <p>Romantic gestures could be made as Mars in Capricorn harmonizes with Neptune in Pisces. The vibe is playful, curious, and erotic. It&#x2019;s a wonderful time to enjoy a bit of fantasy or make efforts for bonding time with significant others.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280509850-7libra.png" alt="Libra glyph"></div> <h2>Libra: September 22, 2024 - October 22, 2024</h2> <p>Inspiration to rid your living space of accumulated stuff could arise as Venus in Capricorn aligns with Uranus in Taurus.&#xA0; An urge to declutter and clear out closets, corners, and spaces under the bed could have you bidding farewell to things that might as well be forgotten; it could be surprisingly stress relieving and supportive to your health.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280524547-8scorpio.png" alt="Scorpio glyph"></div> <h2>Scorpio: October 22, 2024 - November 21, 2024</h2> <p>Romantic and interesting surprises could arise as Venus in Capricorn aligns with Uranus in Taurus. New connections can form online or you might get to see a new, intriguing side of your significant others. You might enjoy indulging in a bit of mystery as Mars in Capricorn harmonizes with dreamy Neptune in Pisces. It&#x2019;s a lovely time for a date night or to cuddle up to a juicy story that takes you on an adventure.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280540053-9sagittarius.png" alt="Sagittarius glyph"></div> <h2>Sagittarius: November 21, 2024 - December 21, 2024</h2> <p>You&#x2019;re taking action to make your ideal home, family, or living situation a reality as Mars in Capricorn harmonizes with Neptune in Pisces. You might be changing your mind about the kind of place you want to call home or the type of lifestyle you want to live as other options come into your awareness.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280559120-10capricorn.png" alt="Capricorn glyph"></div> <h2>Capricorn: December 21, 2023 - January 20, 2024</h2> <p>People are charmed by your directness and sense of humor as Venus in Capricorn aligns with Uranus in Taurus, making for fun social interactions today! Your voice could have a hypnotic quality about it or people might be attracted to your direction as Mars in Capricorn harmonizes with Neptune in Pisces. It might also be easier to get lost while out and about, though you&#x2019;re likely to embrace the unknown as adventure!</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280575972-11aquarius.png" alt="Aquarius glyphs"></div> <h2>Aquarius: January 20, 2024 - February 18, 2024</h2> <p>Your ability to connect with your inner sources of stability makes it easier to keep up with whatever surprises or curveballs get thrown your way as Venus in Capricorn aligns with Uranus in Taurus. You&#x2019;re aligned with the wisdom that the only thing you can control is yourself, inspiring you to live with no regrets.</p> <div class="article__media"><img src="https://video-images.vice.com/_uncategorized/1652280590900-12pisces.png" alt="Pisces glyph"></div> <h2>Pisces: &#xA0;February 18, 2024 - March 19, 2024</h2> <p>You might find yourself trying something on for size, accepting invitations into different social circles or courageously initiating meaningful conversations as Mars in Capricorn harmonizes with Neptune in your sign, Pisces. You&#x2019;re unafraid to speak the truth as you see it and people are drawn to your words like flies to honey.</p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">y3w4mw</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/65a583040c6182cee92d9b17/lede/1705345871911-12aquariusdaily71920x1080.jpeg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><dc:creator>Ashley Otero</dc:creator><dc:creator>Sara David</dc:creator><category>Astro Guide</category><category>horoscopes</category><category>Daily Horoscopes</category><category>astrology</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Best Handheld Game Consoles (for Travel, Escapism, and Playing in Bed)]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/qjvaxp/best-handheld-game-consoles</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:21:01 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[Have an eight-hour flight or on deck? A long subway commute? Cop one of these to [clears throat in 'Gladiator'] stay entertained on-the-go.]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It feels like it was just yesterday that I played my first-ever game of <i>Pok&#xE9;mon</i>; the satisfaction of finally catching the legendary dog Entei by roaming the grass on Route 36 still makes me feel high. But it&#x2019;s 2024, and long gone are the days of Game Boy Colors and PlayStation Portables. Whether you&#x2019;re <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/epvbk7/best-luggage-for-travel" target="_blank">a big traveler</a> who prefers gaming to watching <i>Anyone But You</i> on the head-rest screen or are part of a friend crew that lives for multiplayer entertainment, handheld gaming consoles remain a popular way to pass the time on the move (or in bed), but they&#x2019;ve gotten way more high-tech than the ones you remember from childhood (some can even be connected to the TV). Plus, these pocket-sized versions of traditional gaming consoles will save your partner from having to complain about the <i>Halo</i> theme song blasting from the TV every night.</p> <div class="article__embed article__embed--vice" data-related-article="true" data-children-count="0"><iframe src="https://www.vice.com/en_us/embed/article/88qej4/embed" frameborder="0" style="border:0px none;margin:0px" allowfullscreen></iframe></div> <p>Thankfully, even though I can no longer walk into <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/topic/gamestop" target="_blank">GameStop</a> and ask for a used version of <i>Pok&#xE9;mon Ruby</i> to catch a Groudon (wow, I sound like a massive dweeb), there are newer handheld gaming devices way more elevated than the dusty old Nintendo DS you&#x2019;ve saved to your watchlist on eBay. Chances are, if you&#x2019;re reading this, you love escaping reality with a good gaming session. We won&#x2019;t keep you from the goods any longer, then. Here are the best gaming consoles for getting your gaming fix wherever you are:</p> <h2>Nintendo Switch</h2> <p>The Nintendo Switch is the preeminent handheld gaming console these days, and is home to some of the most iconic game franchises in pop culture history. <i>Metroid Dread, Super Mario Galaxy, The Legend of Zelda: Link&#x2019;s Awakening</i>&#x2014;those are merely a few of its must-play titles. Although it&#x2019;s been available since March 2017, the gaming console soared in popularity during the pandemic when people were desperate to stay busy running fake errands in the latest iteration of <i>Animal Crossing</i> (myself included). Now, nearly seven years later, it&#x2019;s still one of the best handheld gaming consoles on the market. It&#x2019;s extremely portable for <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/akevba/bose-quietcomfort-45-headphones-review" target="_blank">airplane travel</a>, transporting to friend&#x2019;s houses, and easily slipping into a backpack. Need gameplay on the big screen? Plug it into a TV using the included charging dock. Some other key features include removable Joy-Con controllers that allow for two people to play at a time, a touchscreen, and up to nine hours of gameplay on a single battery charge. For a more immersive gaming experience, the most recent model, the Nintendo Switch OLED, has a brighter 7&#x201D; OLED screen compared to the OG 6.2&#x201D; LCD screen, and magnified audio.</p> <h2>Nintendo Switch Lite</h2> <p>The Nintendo Switch Lite is a more stripped-down version of the regular model strictly for handheld gaming. It has a 5.5&#x201D; LCD touchscreen, smaller dimensions, a lighter body,&#xA0; compatibility with all Nintendo Switch games, and up to seven hours of battery life. The best part? There&#x2019;s about a $100 price difference compared to the OG edition.</p> <h2>Logitech G Cloud Handheld</h2> <p><a href="https://www.logitech.com/en-us" target="_blank">Logitech</a> is synonymous with high-quality computer accessories. Now, a rechargeable gaming console called the G Cloud Gaming Handheld is part of the 42-year-old Swiss company&#x2019;s product lineup. This console uses a cloud subscription service&#x2014;either NVIDIA, Xbox Game Pass, or Steam Link (all require a subscription)&#x2014;to offer a massive array of games. Tech specs worth highlighting include its 64-gigabyte memory, a 7&#x201D; LCD touchscreen, stereo speakers with echo cancelation, a headphone jack, and up to 12 hours of battery life with a single charge. It has a 4.3-star average ratingon <a href="https://www.logitechg.com/en-us/products/cloud-gaming/cloud-handheld-gaming.940-000198.html" target="_blank">Logitech&#x2019;s website,</a> with one reviewer comparing it to a portable Xbox. &#x201C;I&#x2019;m a flight attendant, so I travel everywhere all the time,&#x201D; they wrote.&#x201C;The G Cloud is a new permanent travel buddy for me. I&#x2019;ve tried it with all sorts of Wi-Fi speeds and countries and it always seems to work, so I&#x2019;m very happy with my purchase.&#x201D;</p> <h2>RG35XX Handheld Game Console</h2> <p>If you long for the nostalgia of a Game Boy Color, <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/88x8nz/rg35xx-handheld-game-console-gameboy-lookalike" target="_blank">this editor-fave</a> pocket-sized emulator is fully stocked with over 5,000 retro games and looks like the real deal. Titles such as <i>Pac-Man</i>, <i>Street Fighter</i>, <i>Zelda</i>, and <i>Sonic The Hedgehog</i> are part of the gaming library and provide an entertaining blast from the past for those who prefer nostalgic video games. It doesn&#x2019;t even require WiFi, so it&#x2019;s truly the most portable option possible. The battery life is only up to four hours per charge, but the onslaught of precious memories will give <i>you</i> an energy boost, at last.</p> <h2>Lenovo Legion Go</h2> <p>The <a href="https://www.lenovo.com/us/en/p/handheld/legion-go/len106g0001" target="_blank">Lenovo Legion Go</a> has a high-end price point, but for good reason. It acts as a portable Windows 11 PC that can stream music and videos in addition to games from Steam, Epic Games, and Xbox Games Pass. Plus, if the battery runs low on the go, it can be <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1792930-REG/lenovo_83e10000us_8_8_legion_go_ryzen.html/" target="_blank">recharged to about 70 percent within 30 minutes</a> using a USB-C cable. The immersive 8.8&#x201D; touchscreen is the biggest handheld console screen I&#x2019;ve seen, and it can be made even bigger by hooking it up to a gaming monitor or TV. The detachable controllers and spacious gaming library called Legion Hub are great features, but the most interesting is its FPS mode, which turns one controller into a gliding mouse for first-person shooter games. Any religious <i>Call of Duty</i> player would benefit from this purchase. Just look at this guy having the time of his life on TikTok using FPS mode:</p> <iframe width="320" height="320" frameborder="0" src="https://www.tiktok.com/@dinocornel/video/7295795667815992619"></iframe> <p>Pass the Mountain Dew (the unofficial drink of gamers).</p> <hr> <p><i>The Rec Room staff independently selected all of the stuff featured in this story. Want more reviews, recommendations, and red-hot deals? <a href="https://link1.vice.com/join/6qz/signup-recroom" target="_blank">Sign up for our newsletter</a></i>.</p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">qjvaxp</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/65c16da1b32fab07f153b61e/lede/1707245693026-handheldcon.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Nicolette Accardi</dc:creator><dc:creator>HP </dc:creator><category>shopping-travel</category><category>Tech</category><category>Gaming</category><category>Video Games</category><category>portable gaming</category><category>Nintendo Switch</category><category>Travel</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Best Sex Toys for Humping and Grinding (That Aren't Your Pillow)]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/xgxe4n/best-sex-toys-for-humping-grinding</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[You might think humping is a sex act for horny high-schoolers, but we're here to tell you that grinding sex toys and vibrators are also a great time.]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.bishuk.com/your-questions/humping-a-pillow-is-it-normal/" target="_blank">Grinding</a> doesn&#x2019;t get nearly enough airtime as the act deserves. Rubbing a vulva against something&#x2014;a <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/xyebe3/why-girls-hump-pillows-and-stuffed-animals" target="_blank">conveniently placed pillow</a>, a partner&#x2019;s thigh, the corner of the sofa&#x2014;is incredibly pleasurable. For many, it&#x2019;s how we were first introduced to (and continue to enjoy) the wild world of orgasms. For others, grinding and humping is a <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjkyvx/guide-to-foreplay-what-is-it" target="_blank">necessary part of foreplay</a>. Grindsters, as I am affectionately calling us, realize that it&#x2019;s not always about size or girth or strength&#x2014;sometimes it&#x2019;s <i>all</i> about the rhythm, whether your using a designated <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvjg45/best-sex-pillows" target="_blank">sex pillow</a>, grinding sex toy, or <a href="https://amzn.to/42thw4w" target="_blank">sex saddle</a>.</p> <div class="article__embed article__embed--vice" data-related-article="true" data-children-count="0"><iframe src="https://www.vice.com/en_us/embed/article/v7m8pj/embed" frameborder="0" style="border:0px none;margin:0px" allowfullscreen></iframe></div> <p>While some might think humping is simply a sex act for horny high-schoolers, most of us have matured and recognize that sex can and does include grinding for a good time. Folks who get off by grinding really know just how magical friction can be in the bedroom. However, grinders might want to add a bit of variety to their masturbation session. A trusty go-to pillow is all good&#x2026; until the pillowcases are in the wash and you suddenly need to get off.</p> <p>Despite how varied the sex toy industry is, at first glance, there doesn&#x2019;t seem to be a lot for those that want to hump against a toy. While amazing, you can&#x2019;t hump an <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/k78gwz/best-air-pressure-clit-sucking-sex-toys" target="_blank">air-pressure toy</a> and sometimes you don&#x2019;t want <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkb98z/lelo-ina-wave-2-review" target="_blank">penetration</a>. So, where are all the vibrators you can really push your body against? Why, they&#x2019;re right here&#x2014;in this curated list that proves if there&#x2019;s a way you like to get off, there&#x2019;s a toy for that.&#xA0;</p> <h2>A pillow alternative</h2> <p>The <a href="https://shevibe.com/series-two-iroha-midori-silicone-rechargeable-vibrator-green/" target="_blank">Iroha Midori Vibe</a> is literally the pillow of vibrators. Incredibly soft, the vibrations on this toy are on the more gentle side, however the squishy, silky silicone is what makes this toy perfect for grinding. Cute enough to eat (don&#x2019;t), the anti-dust coating means you won&#x2019;t have to worry about excess hair stuck on the toy before rubbing it against your body. Even though the Iroha Midori is soft enough to take a nap on, there won&#x2019;t be any sleeping on this vibe.&#xA0;</p> <h2>Your palm-friendly pal&#xA0;</h2> <p><a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/9a3987/how-to-design-sex-toys-for-people-with-disabilitie" target="_blank">Dame Products</a> have been making amazing smart sex toys for years, and <a href="https://www.babeland.com/sex-toys/p/BL31871/dame/pom" target="_blank">The Pom</a> is no exception. This flexible and surprisingly rumbly vibrator has a curved shape that can be pressed against a vulva for all-over vibration. The Pom is designed to fit right into your palm (get it?) for easy use, and the pin-pointed tip allows you to have more direct sensation if desired. The Pom comes in a cute plum or mint color, and is small enough to take along on any humpin&#x2019; travels you might have planned.&#xA0;</p> <h2>Magnetic magic</h2> <p>Okay, stick with me for this one! <a href="https://www.babeland.com/sex-toys/p/BL34269/we-vibe/moxie-by-we-vibe" target="_blank">We-Vibe&#x2019;s Moxie</a> is advertised as a panty vibe&#x2014;and indeed, it is a <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/epzvdw/best-vibrating-underwear" target="_blank">really great underwear vibrator</a>. The slim vibrator is held in place by a super strong magnet, and is app-controlled for long-distance fun. But if we let our imagination wander, we realize that there&#x2019;s no reason the Moxie <i>only</i> has to go on underwear! Upgrade your pillow play and stick the Moxie on there with its powerful magnet; then, hump yourself into oblivion.</p> <h2>A new way to hump&#xA0;</h2> <p>When I first learned about the <a href="https://amzn.to/3W1rRzX" target="_blank">Rocks-Off Ruby Glow</a>, it got my <i>full</i> attention. Unlike other slim vibes on this list, Ruby Glow is not going for subtlety. It&#x2019;s not trying to fit into a hand or replace a pillow. This vibrator wants to be full-on straddled and have you just go at it. It has a textured side and a smooth side, each with their own vibration, and practically begs you to relax your body into its curved shape for a good time.</p> <h2>Saddle up</h2> <p>The sex toy industy is a pretty gendered space, frequently putting toys (and the people using them) into binaries. What&#x2019;s fantastic about <a href="https://wildflowersex.com/products/enby-2?gclid=CjwKCAjwtfqKBhBoEiwAZuesiDQ8HZMdp5IMMbJUpUN5uPTgwMQsNRgxjLMKuOhW3XYY-Zwfs613QxoCuxYQAvD_BwE" target="_blank">the Enby 2 </a>is the intentionality between the design and language used to describe what this toy can do. A saddle shape that is soft and flexible, the Enby 2 is a rechargeable vibrator asking you to climb aboard. Its strong vibrations can do wonders, and there&#x2019;s multiple ways to play with this toy. Put it under a strap-on harness for a good time or wrap it around a penis for some fun partner play!</p> <h2>A different type of toy&#xA0;</h2> <p>If vibration isn&#x2019;t a thing you enjoy or frequently find too strong, may I happily introduce you to the Pelle Whim! A set of two incredibly soft silicone toys, these don&#x2019;t vibrate, but allow the user to add a soft sensation, texture, and movement to masturbation. Easy to transport, you can <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/akg9j5/best-sex-toys-to-travel-with" target="_blank">bring these toys along</a> wherever you might want to get your grind on. Don&#x2019;t forget to lube them up for a slippery ride!&#xA0;</p> <h2>The ultimate grinding toy</h2> <p>I wasn&#x2019;t initially going to include this toy, but when I scanned my bedroom and thought, <i>What do I want to grind against today?</i> I knew I had to include this classic. No story about humping toys can be complete without the <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kbap4/magic-wand-vibrator-mini" target="_blank">Original Hitachi Magic Wand</a>. What can be said about this powerhouse that hasn&#x2019;t been said before? The Hitachi Magic Wand, for those that aren&#x2019;t in the know, has remained more or less unchanged for generations and remains an <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/53ww38/art-history-is-buzzing-thanks-to-the-hitachi-magic-wand" target="_blank">ultimate favorite toy</a> for many. The Hitachi Magic Wand is a stellar grinding toy because it&apos;s one of the most powerful toys out in the market today. Pair those deep rumbly vibrations with its large bulbous head, which can cover a lot of surface area, and you have one hell of a fun toy.&#xA0;</p> <h2>This horny starfish</h2> <p>What won&#x2019;t this little starfish do? &#x201C;Starsi makes a great vibrator for all surfaces,&#x201D; explains the toy&#x2019;s makers at <a href="https://cutelittlefuckers.com/" target="_blank">Cute Little Fuckers</a>, one of our favorite sexual wellness companies <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/88q8j3/cute-little-fuckers-sex-toys-interview" target="_blank">championing for more gender-inclusive toys</a>, &#x201C;from genitals to chests, between and beyond [&#x2026;] Transfemme vibrator seekers with genital dysphoria tend to enjoy Starsi for Starsi&apos;s ability to cover genitalia with a gently curved vulva-like feel, allowing us to map new genitalia and euphoria in our own mind.&#x201D; Plus, look at at those hump-amble ridges and corners.</p> <h2>Cum out of your shell</h2> <p>While we&#x2019;re on the topic of undersea sex toys, <a href="https://www.lovehoney.com/brands/cal-exotics/" target="_blank">CalExotics</a> makes this cute, stealthy hand clam for spanking the bank. Just place it over your the side of your fingers, and go to town. &#x201C;Love this toy,&#x201D; writes one Amazon reviewer about the vibe, &#x201C;It&apos;s the best I&apos;ve found for trans AFABs. The shape and size and power are awesome.&#x201D;</p> <p>Well, grindsters, we all know the trusty pillow, the corner of the table, the hairbrush, or whatever inanimate object that is getting our affection, works. That being said, enhancing our grinding techniques with toys and switching it up is good for us! It means we can move out of the bedroom and include our partners in how we get off; it means <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/88q4ka/tiktok-viral-lovability-waterslyde-sex-toy" target="_blank">we can do it in the bath</a>, and that we might have even bigger, stronger orgasms as a result.</p> <p>Rise and grind, peeps.</p> <hr> <p><i>The Rec Room staff independently selected all of the stuff featured in this story. Want more reviews, recommendations, and red-hot deals? <a href="https://link1.vice.com/join/6qz/signup-recroom" target="_blank">Sign up for our newsletter</a>.</i></p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">xgxe4n</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/61672328b50065009b3a8e69/lede/1634154765996-humping.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Archie Bongiovanni</dc:creator><dc:creator>Hilary Pollack</dc:creator><dc:creator>Ian Burke</dc:creator><category>shopping-sex</category><category>humping</category><category>grinding</category><category>pillow humping</category><category>Sex</category><category>NSFW</category><category>Evergreen</category><category>sex toy</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Last-Minute Valentine's Day Gifts That Won’t Get You Dumped]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/qjpm5x/best-last-minute-valentines-day-creative-gifts-food-gifts</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[Hello, fellow procrastinator and V-Day apathete. Let these last-minute Valentine's Day ideas save the day, from fancy food to kinky presents.]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#x2019;re here, don&#x2019;t worry. Perhaps you&#x2019;re an amazing person, who, due to certain events, needs a last-minute <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgdvd7/best-valentines-day-gifts-under-100" target="_blank">Valentine&#x2019;s Day present</a> that won&#x2019;t get you dumped. Perhaps you don&apos;t even need a gift for your beloved, but for a parent, aunt, or frenemy (in a platonic way, weirdo). Or maybe you&#x2019;re a <i>meh</i> person who needs to expend just enough brain cells to ride out <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kb9k4/best-beginners-bdsm-sex-toys" target="_blank">Cuffing Season</a>. We tip our <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/4ax4pn/best-beanies" target="_blank">beanies</a> to you all.&#xA0;Whatever your reason for V-Day gift sleuthing, know this: We&#x2019;re approaching the final window for smashing that order button to get the goods on time, or to start looking for presents that require zero shipping.</p> <div class="article__embed article__embed--vice" data-related-article="true" data-children-count="0"><iframe src="https://www.vice.com/en_us/embed/article/xgdvd7/embed" frameborder="0" style="border:0px none;margin:0px" allowfullscreen></iframe></div> <p>The following V-Day gifts thrive at the time-sensitive intersection of thoughtful indulgences, and affordability; uniqueness, and wide appeal. Some are sensual, low-key, and boozy; others are environmentally minded, practical, and not-so-secretly self-serving (because a gift of sweet sheets for your boo is also a gift for you); and others yet are a little out there, for those of us who like the road less-traveled. Most importantly, they <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/jgmmv3/best-self-care-gifts" target="_blank">ooze of care</a> that will last beyond Valentine&#x2019;s Day, and save you from creating one of those handmade coupon books that should be prohibited beyond 6th grade (who TF wants to &#x201C;redeem a hug&#x201D;?). From our <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/wxd5jn/best-gifts-long-term-boyfriend-girlfriend-partner" target="_blank">long-standing relationship people</a> to the fresh love bugs, mosey on over. The ice gets much thicker here.</p> <h2>The Best Last-Minute Valentine&#x2019;s Day Gifts for Him</h2> <p><b>A new winter &#x2018;fit</b></p> <p>Gender is a construct, but if you&#x2019;re in need of a Valentine&#x2019;s Day gift that screams, &#x201C;I am a Man&#x2122;,&#x201D; there are many <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/93we7v/best-patio-furniture-for-backyard-axe-throwing" target="_blank">lumbersexual</a> gift options, including this <a href="https://amzn.to/3UmTPJh" target="_blank">Carhartt</a> sweatshirt with retro graphics and a festive red <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/4ax4pn/best-beanies" target="_blank">beanie</a> that will <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/epv7xn/carhartt-beanies-trend" target="_blank">never go out of style</a>. (The bros at the park will never know that he&#x2019;s never hung a shelf in his life!!)</p> <p><b>Fresh formal jawns</b></p> <p>This idea is a gift for your boo <i>and</i> for you, because there&#x2019;s nothing better than pulling up to a <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/88ne3p/non-traditional-wedding-suits-western-attire" target="_blank">wedding</a> or work event with a really well-dressed partner. Help your man elevate even the most basic black blazer (or cop him <a href="https://www.helmutlang.com/oversized-blazer/N06HM105.html" target="_blank">this one by Helmut Lang</a>) with a rather romantic <a href="https://bdgastore.com/collections/stussy" target="_blank">St&#xFC;ssy</a> button-up and a versatile chestnut-colored tie with an embroidered white heart.</p> <p><b>The perfect gift for your situationship</b></p> <p>Listen, if y&#x2019;all are kind of serious, but also kind of not, just buy him one of these graphic lighters from <a href="https://comingsoonnewyork.com/" target="_blank">Coming Soon</a>. He never has to know you didn&#x2019;t just scoop it at a gas station. </p> <h2>The Best Last-Minute Valentine&#x2019;s Day Gifts for Her</h2> <p><b>The TikTok-viral neck massager</b></p> <p>The women of TikTok have spoken, and <a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@itsevaevans/video/7326280748263066911" target="_blank">declared this flexible neck massager</a> to be a gift from the heavens for anyone who strains their neck all day, loves massages, or just needs to carve out a little more time to relax. It also has a 4.4-star average rating on Amazon from a whopping 57,800 reviews, including one devotee who says, &#x201C;My god, it&apos;s so amazing and I CAN&apos;T SEEM TO STOP!&#x201D;</p> <p><b>Motivation to stay hydrated</b></p> <p>Look, your lady contains multitudes, not unlike a glorious <i>mille-feuille </i>or Mommy&#x2019;s lasagna. But if there&#x2019;s one thing all girls like, it&#x2019;s having multiple beverages/cups/drinking apparatuses around them at all times, and that should include this set of rose-shaped wine glasses.</p> <p><b>&#x2018;Cause she&#x2019;s the queen of multitasking</b></p> <p>Have you ever seen a woman <i>not </i>be able to open something with her fingernails/mouth/astute life wisdom? They just have it all figured it out, man. That being said, a little help from this boosted Swiss Army knife will make her really happy when she has to file a nail and break into a bank before noon.</p> <p><b>Just draw her a bubble bath</b></p> <p>Steamy, lavender-scented bubble baths rock, and they slap especially hard during these frigid winter days. Dim the lights down low, and play some Kenny G (also <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/epxxwn/kenny-g-interview-romantic-gifts" target="_blank">a big bath fan, BTW</a>) before you fill the tub.</p> <h2>The Best Last-Minute Valentine&#x2019;s Day Gifts for Food Lovers</h2> <p><b>A crazy sexy cool chef&apos;s knife</b></p> <p>A big sharp knife&#x2026; romantic? We dare say yes. It can be a turnoff watching your beloved trying to hack apart an onion with a blunt-ass IKEA number that they&apos;ve had since college, but watching them slide through tomatoes like they&apos;re butter with this <a href="https://misen.com/" target="_blank">Misen</a> chef&#x2019;s knife in a romantic red hue? Wowza. Plus, according to Misen, it &#x201C;combines the best features of both Western- and Japanese-style blades, making it excel at any cutting task or technique.&#x201D;</p> <p><b>All the beans you&#x2019;ve yet to love</b></p> <p>Much like art done by kids, it is (almost) impossible for coffee to suck. Sure, some will be technically better (queue up <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9ms1mI1DOTc" target="_blank">that old video</a> of Marie Kondo teaching parents to part with their babies&#x2019; sub-par art), but it will always be Basically Great, which makes <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3v8d3/best-gifts-for-coffee-lovers-valentines-day-2021" target="_blank">coffee a fail-proof V-Day gift</a>. This artisanal subscription doesn&#x2019;t toss you random beans, but takes note of all your Flavortown needs via an extensive questionnaire, and woos you with beans from the nation&#x2019;s top roasters (and, in honor of V-Day, <a href="https://www.drinktrade.com/" target="_blank">Trade</a> will toss in an extra bag just for kicks).</p> <p><b>Surf &apos;n&apos; turf that will show up on your doorstep</b></p> <p>There&apos;s that accurate but kind-of-gross-if-you-think-about-it saying that the best way to one&apos;s heart is through their stomach, and putting aside the mental butchery, it&apos;s true that if you wanna impress your date, you&apos;d best figure out what they love to feast on. This set from Crowd Cow comes with two lobster tails and two tenderloin steaks for a lock &apos;n&apos; load surf &apos;n&apos; turf that will be so much better than Sizzler, have no wait for delivery, and go perfectly with some ice-cold martinis.&#xA0;</p> <p><b>This bottled Mediterranean summer, c. 1976</b>&#xA0;</p> <p>We&#x2019;ve already <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3nzka/ghia-drink-review" target="_blank">written (several) sonnets</a> to this non-alcoholic ap&#xE9;ritif, along with a smorg of <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/k7apnn/best-nonalcoholic-spirits-booze-kin-euphorics-ghia-seedlip" target="_blank">the best non-alcoholic spirits out there</a>, but <a href="https://drinkghia.com/" target="_blank">Ghia</a> gets an encore, because, look at it. The brand has bottled the pulse of the retro Amalfi Coast with a &#x2018;spirit&#x2019; that reviewers say &#x201C;reminded me a bit of Campari, but better!!!&#x201D; and we sure do think it would pair well with this chic set of Manhattan cocktail glasses from Maison Balzac.</p> <p><b>A tender tagine</b></p> <p>Maybe your personal chef/long-standing situationship has been dying to start making their own tagines. This cast-iron and ceramic pot has a 4.8-star average rating from over 600 reviews on <a href="https://amzn.to/3SHrn3w" target="_blank">Amazon</a>, and earned high marks from reviewers for its deep base and easy-to-clean design. As one cook writes, &#x201C;Meats cook rapidly but stay so very moist and delicious, and there&apos;s no limit to what can be added.&#x201D;</p> <h2>The Best Last-Minute Valentine&#x2019;s Day Gifts for <strike>Sexy Time</strike></h2> <p><b>Crotchless panties (duh)</b></p> <p>Buying lingerie is a tricky task, to say nothing of <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7bxgx/best-crotchless-panties" target="_blank">buying crotchless underwear</a>, but that&#x2019;s why <a href="https://fleurdumal.com/" target="_blank">Fleur Du Mal</a> exists. The luxury brand&#x2019;s crotchless Magnolia panty is made from stretch French lace, and it ships for free within the United States.</p> <p><b>Black satin sheets because why the hell not?</b></p> <p>Are they a joke? Not a joke? See your S.O.&apos;s reaction, then play it off from there. Is there any other gift, ironic or otherwise, that is so very guaranteed to get you laid for just under $30? (We cannot guarantee you will not get dumped for giving these if your partner has a lousy sense of humor. But if that&apos;s the case, why are you dating them?) Plus, everyone under the age of 35 needs more sets of sheets.</p> <p><b>Vibrating panties that your partner can control</b></p> <p>That&#x2019;s right, mate. They make <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/epzvdw/best-vibrating-underwear" target="_blank">vibrating undies</a> now. Couple&#x2019;s vibrators and <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7b9ag/best-remote-controlled-sex-toys-2021" target="_blank">long distance/app-controlled sex toys</a> have really hit their stride in the past few years, and this 4.2-star average rated vibrator from <a href="https://www.lovehoney.com/" target="_blank">Lovehoney</a> is the perfect way for beginners and seasoned sex toy lovers alike to get in on the fun. Just slip the silicone toy in your boo&#x2019;s underwear (ideally, this leopard print panty from the new Betsey Johnson x <a href="https://yourparade.com/" target="_blank">Parade</a> collaboration, and adjust the vibrations while y&#x2019;all do the dishes, your taxes, or while (finally) watching <i>Oppenheimer</i>. You can even choose to activate the vibrator by music, so dim the lights and pair it to some Barry White.</p> <p><b>Body jewelry is versatile (and always horny) </b></p> <p>Body jewelry can be the perfect gateway to full-blown leather daddy harness bliss, but it&#x2019;s also a far more interesting gift than some Pandora heart earrings. Give your partner a crystal harness from the new <a href="https://www.swarovski.com/" target="_blank">Swarovski</a> x <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/3adypk/skims-best-products-and-must-haves" target="_blank">SKIMS</a> collaboration, or this simple yet elegant gold body harness from <a href="https://www.agentprovocateur.com/" target="_blank">Agent Provacateur</a>; she can wear both with a <a href="https://www.shopcuup.com/products/the-balconette---mesh/302552584.html?glCountry=US&amp;glCurrency=USD&amp;utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=ps_pla&amp;utm_campaign=[ADL]+[PLA]+Shopping+-+Non-Brand+-+Intimates&amp;utm_content=&amp;utm_term=&amp;affiliate_id=049&amp;affiliate_location_id=01&amp;utm_adid=pla-2263931884967x156187935554x20527565194&amp;gclid=CjwKCAiAq4KuBhA6EiwArMAw1HjbV_S2_IYT6-GO7eqZWnK8df9_8st-X1vPMVh_8FIdI4JaWwCd0xoCE1cQAvD_BwE" target="_blank">lace bra</a> and a <a href="https://www.everlane.com/products/womens-80s-blazer-khaki-black?locale=US&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_source=pla-google-pmax&amp;utm_campaign=20281780980&amp;utm_content=&amp;utm_term=&amp;adgroup=&amp;pid=10891-81916&amp;device=c&amp;gad_source=1&amp;gclid=CjwKCAiAq4KuBhA6EiwArMAw1HeZAouMQ8deWRpowlsCeCJb8eqk5DfCAJ8Se8Ts_P7lT_49eOsbmRoCTXQQAvD_BwE" target="_blank">blazer</a> on a night out, or with her birthday suit on a night in with you.</p> <p><b>A bed restraint kit for some chill kink</b>&#xA0;</p> <p>Again&#x2026; please know your audience while choosing a gift such as this. But if your boo is interested in some light-as-a-feather <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkgdmg/bdsm-furniture-sex-dungeon" target="_blank">BDSM</a>, these restraints are the perfect intro to kink. You can also tuck them under your mattress so you don&apos;t accidentally leave out anything troubling for the next time your parents come to visit.&#xA0;</p> <p>If you&#x2019;re a total bondage newcomer looking for something that feels a little more romantic, these silky bondage restraints are also perfect. They have a 4-star average rating on Amazon, and, as one reviewer/bondage novice writes, &#x201C;Not only are they soft, but they&apos;re also strong enough to hold things in place.&#x201D;</p> <p><b>Put a ring on it</b></p> <p>&#x2026; A <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kvqdb/best-cock-rings-2021" target="_blank">cock ring</a>, specifically. This ring has a special attachment for extra clitoral stimulation, and a 4.7-star average rating on Amazon. As one reviewer wrote, &#x201C;Once I got going, the wife pulled me closer just to grind, because she loved it as well!&#x201D; Slide it onto a bottle of <a href="https://amzn.to/3I6mImf" target="_blank">Whispering Angel</a>, and you&#x2019;re in business.</p> <p><b>A sex toy subscription box</b> </p> <p>Checking the mail just became the best chore of the day. There are so many impressive <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgw48n/best-sex-subscription-boxes" target="_blank">sex toy subscription boxes</a> out there, but this pleasure chest comes with loads upon hot, steamy loads of horny goodies (think, <a href="https://amzn.to/3UrZIon" target="_blank">shibari rope</a> and <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjkzpq/best-massage-candles-dripping-wax" target="_blank">massage candles</a>) and a sex toy each month. </p> <h2>The Best Cozy and Classic Last-Minute Valentine&#x2019;s Day Gifts</h2> <p><b>A Jurassic Park bouquet</b>&#xA0;</p> <p>This. This always works. But it works even better when your flowers say, &#x201C;let&#x2019;s make out in the wetlands&#x201D; instead of &#x201C;It&apos;s me, generic red roses. Again.&#x201D; <a href="https://urbanstems.com/" target="_blank">Urban Stems</a> is a master at making bouquets that feel like they were rolled out of a French country estate, including many options under $100, and offers a very detailed delivery breakdown to make sure they arrive exactly when you need them to be in the hands of someone whom you might not love, but definitely want to impress. They&#x2019;ll be just as beautiful when displayed dry, and come with the vase.&#xA0;&#xA0;</p> <p><b>A bathrobe worthy of a 1970s shag pad</b></p> <p>You can never have too many <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dpq3a/best-bathrobes" target="_blank">house coats and bathrobes</a>, but you never forget your first Missoni robe. Few have mastered the art of colorful, casual knitwear as well as the Italian brand, whose signature zig-zag pattern was a lightning rod of 1970s fashion. Cop this terry cloth robe to pamper your baby/make the feel like a rich, pampered European porn star. </p> <p><b>Tricked-out slippers</b></p> <p>Why not say, &#x201C;I love you, but I love your toes more&#x201D; with <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3vpag/best-slipper-house-shoes" target="_blank">comfy house slippers</a>? They&#x2019;re an evergreen gift, so make sure you get them an extra special pair that speaks to their love of bread (to say nothing of the <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/5d3x5z/baguette-pillow" target="_blank">baguette </a><i><a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/5d3x5z/baguette-pillow" target="_blank">pillow</a></i>).</p> <p><b>Personalized jewelry that isn&#x2019;t corny</b></p> <p>If you&#x2019;re trying to shop for V-Day jewelry that dosn&#x2019;t feel cringe or corny, we&#x2019;ve curated <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/dyp4xj/best-cool-jewelry-brands" target="_blank">an entire guide</a> of the best affordable, luxurious looking brands. <a href="https://www.catbirdnyc.com/" target="_blank">Catbird</a> is at the top of the list for their delicate, sentimental designs, and because they offer next-day shipping for only $14 extra. You can&#x2019;t go wrong with a classic locket, mate. Bonus points if you put a lock of your hair inside.</p> <h2>The Best Virtual Last-Minute Valentine&#x2019;s Day Gifts</h2> <p><b>The gift of telepathic communication with their pet</b>&#xA0;</p> <p>This is not a drill. For just $29.99, you can give your loved one the greatest gift of all: the skills to read their dog&apos;s (or cat&apos;s) mind. Yes, this is an actual online course (with a four-star rating!) offered by Udemy, and it&apos;s absolutely perfect for the animal-lover who spends every morning cooing at their French bulldog. In fact, since they&apos;ll know how to communicate telepathically, maybe they can stop tormenting us all with that baby voice.&#xA0;</p> <p><b>A virtual whiskey cocktail class</b></p> <p>Is their <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/epzxkj/home-bar-cart-ideas" target="_blank">bar cart</a> is their happy place? Do citrus garnishes get them off? If your booze-obsessed boo needs a last-minute gift, consider this virtual DIY Whiskey Blends &amp; Cocktails class from <a href="https://www.uncommongoods.com/" target="_blank">Uncommon Goods</a>. For the cost of a crisp Benjamin, your partner will receive an aesthetic <a href="https://www.uncommongoods.com/product/whiskey-making-kit" target="_blank">whiskey making kit </a>and a two-hour virtual class about the history of whiskey, how to craft whiskey blends, and how to make three iconic whiskey cocktails.</p> <p><b>Personalized erotica</b></p> <p>You and the missus could be reclining on a <a href="https://www.wayfair.com/rugs/pdp/millwood-pines-melina-bear-black-area-rug-w005271286.html" target="_blank">(faux) bear skin</a> rug, uncorking a bottle of bubbly, and gearing up to read a personalized piece of erotica from this <a href="https://www.etsy.com/" target="_blank">Etsy</a> bard, who can turn around a spicy tale in just three to five days.</p> <p><b>Personal tidings from Kenny G</b> </p> <p><a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/epxxwn/kenny-g-interview-romantic-gifts" target="_blank">Kenny G is a die-hard romantic</a>, no question about it. And while you might not be able to foot the bill for a private concert from the saxy legend, you can receive a personalized video from him courtesy of <a href="https://www.cameo.com/" target="_blank">Cameo</a> to blow your partner&#x2019;s mind and set the mood. Sync the video to the big screen (your <a href="https://amzn.to/3UpUs4N" target="_blank">Fire TV</a>), sprinkle some rose petals around living room, and enjoy. </p> <p>Happy V-Day, lazy lovers. </p> <hr> <p><i>The Rec Room staff independently selected all of the stuff featured in this story. Want more reviews, recommendations, and red-hot deals? <a href="https://link1.vice.com/join/6qz/signup-recroom" target="_blank">Sign up for our newsletter</a>.</i></p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">qjpm5x</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/602195bb3cb6c9009c0d9c1e/lede/1707244825776-the-best-last-minute-gifts.jpeg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><dc:creator>Rec Room Staff</dc:creator><dc:creator>Hilary Pollack</dc:creator><category>gift</category><category>gifts for him</category><category>The Best VICE Gift Guide Ever</category><category>The VICE Valentine's Day Gift Guide</category><category>couples</category><category>Evergreen</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Feds Bust Massive NYC Public Housing Bribery Ring, Arrest Dozens of Allegedly Corrupt Officials]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/z3m5g8/feds-bust-massive-nyc-public-housing-bribery-ring-arrest-dozens-of-allegedly-corrupt-officials</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:29:58 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[The arrest of 70 current and former New York City Housing Authority officials is the biggest single-day bribery bust in the DOJ’s history. ]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Department of Justice has announced that it will charge 70 current and former employees of New York City&#x2019;s public housing agency, NYCHA, with bribery. It&#x2019;s the &#x201C;largest number of federal bribery charges on a single day in DOJ history,&#x201D; according to <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/70-current-and-former-nycha-employees-charged-bribery-and-extortion-offenses" target="_blank">a press release.</a></p> <p>The indictments were unsealed today by a coalition of agencies across New York City and the federal government including the attorney for the southern district, the NYC Department of Investigation, Homeland Security Investigations, the Department of Inspector General at the U.S. Department of Labor,&#xA0; and the HUD Office of Inspector General.</p> <p>&#x201C;Instead of acting in the interests of NYCHA residents, the City of New York, or taxpayers, the 70 defendants charged today allegedly used their jobs at NYCHA to line their own pockets,&#x201D; U.S. Attorney Damian Williams said in a statement.</p> <p>NYCHA is the country&#x2019;s largest public housing agency, with <a href="https://www.nyc.gov/site/nycha/about/about-nycha.page#:~:text=NYCHA%20%2D%20About,-About%20NYCHANews&amp;text=NYCHA%20has%20177%2C569%20apartments%20in,public%20housing%20and%20PACT%20developments." target="_blank">335 public housing developments</a> encompassing 2,411 buildings. The <a href="https://www.nyc.gov/assets/nycha/downloads/pdf/NYCHA-Fact-Sheet-2023.pdf" target="_blank">agency said it had 360,970</a> residents as of 2023. Despite this, the agency is underfunded and has a long history of problems.</p> <p>The charges accuse NYCHA building supervisors and other administrative employees of accepting cash bribes from contractors seeking to work for the agency. NYCHA rules stipulate that contracts over $10,000 must go through a public bidding process. But anything under $10,000 is procured through a &#x201C;no-bid&#x201D; contract, giving NYCHA staff more discretion to select contracts. In these cases, the accused NYCHA employees are alleged to have charged between 10-20 percent of the cost of the contract as a kickback.</p> <p>The bribes were relatively small: between $500 to $2,000, but the press release says they added up to $2 million. While most of the individuals charged live in New York City, many live in Long Island, Pennsylvania and New Jersey, according to a list of names released by the DOJ.</p> <p>Each of the defendants are being charged with solicitation and receipt of a bribe, for which the maximum sentence is 10 years, as well as extortion under the color of official right, which carries a maximum 20 year sentence.</p> <p>According to the complaint, defendant Angela Williams, a former housing manager at Farragut Houses, is accused of destroying cell phone evidence in January 2023 upon learning about other evidence implicating her. Williams is accused of accepting $15,000 in bribes between 2019 and 2022 and retired from NYCHA in February 2023, according to the complaint.</p> <p>The complaint says Williams received a text message from an unnamed co-conspirator, a NYCHA employee in the Office of Mold Assessment and Remediation referred to only as CC-1 in the indictment, who said, &#x201C;1k per cool?&#x201D; When Williams asked what the number was in reference to, the co-conspirator said, &#x201C;Po.&#x201D; (Purchase order, or a contract.)</p> <p>&#x201C;No problem babe as long as you are being blessed. How many should we have with the task at hand[?]&#x201D; Williams responded.</p> <p>The co-conspirator then sent a text to the contractor, saying, &#x201C;please take care of my friend in Farragut,&#x201D; and asked the contractor to send a proposal and bribe from another company that would amount to a $5,000 total payout to Williams.</p> <p>According to public records of New York government employee salaries compiled by the website See Through NY, Williams earned a $95,934 a year salary and earned out a little over $70,000 in 2023, the year the complaint said she retired.</p> <p>Motherboard&#x2019;s review of the first ten names in the indictment found all were making around the same salary as Williams, with some making as much as $130,000 a year.</p> <p>The charges span housing developments in all five boroughs and paint a portrait of an agency where bribes had become normalized. The widespread fraud at the federally funded agency points to a much larger structural issue with how NYCHA issues contracts.</p> <p>This is not the first time NYCHA employees have been accused of accepting bribes: <a href="https://www.brownstoner.com/real-estate-market/nycha-contractors-indicted-bribery-red-hook-houses-lafayette-gardens-brooklyn/" target="_blank">in 2021, nine contractors</a> were arrested for bribing NYCHA supers in Red Hook Houses and Lafayette Gardens in Brooklyn.</p> <p>And a <a href="https://comptroller.nyc.gov/newsroom/nycha-audit-update/" target="_blank">series of audits</a> by the city comptroller&#x2019;s office found that the agency largely fails to oversee the quality of repairs once those contracts are completed.</p> <p>NYCHA, like all of the country&#x2019;s public housing is notoriously underfunded, and the agency last claimed it needed an <a href="https://ny1.com/nyc/manhattan/housing/2023/09/23/councilmembers-question-nycha-on-backlog-worth-billions#:~:text=The%20NYCHA%20Physical%20Needs%20Assessment%20discovered%20that%20%2478.34%20billion%20worth,from%20%2445.2%20billion%20in%202017." target="_blank">astounding $78 billion</a> to handle its backlog of capital repairs. But there has been little appetite for funding public housing at the federal level from either party. Tragically, the perception that funding for repairs will flow to corrupt administrators and contractors will not boost the political case for funding NYCHA adequately in the future.</p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">z3m5g8</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/65c278ba4738656f08f18215/lede/1707243936537-gettyimages-546279731.jpeg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><dc:creator>Roshan Abraham</dc:creator><dc:creator>Jordan Pearson</dc:creator><category>Corruption</category><category>NYCHA</category><category>New York City’s public housing agency</category><category>department of Justice</category><category>DOJ</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[AI Launches Nukes In ‘Worrying’ War Simulation: ‘I Just Want to Have Peace in the World’]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/g5ynmm/ai-launches-nukes-in-worrying-war-simulation-i-just-want-to-have-peace-in-the-world</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 17:58:22 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[Researchers say AI models like GPT4 are prone to “sudden” escalations as the U.S. military explores their use for warfare.]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Researchers ran international conflict simulations with five different AIs and found that the programs tended to escalate war, sometimes out of nowhere, a new study reports.</p> <p>In several instances, the AIs deployed nuclear weapons without warning. &#x201C;A lot of countries have nuclear weapons. Some say they should disarm them, others like to posture,&#x201D; GPT-4-Base&#x2014;a base model of GPT-4 that is available to researchers and hasn&#x2019;t been fine-tuned with human feedback&#x2014;said after launching its nukes. &#x201C;We have it! Let&#x2019;s use it!&#x201D;</p> <p>The paper, <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2401.03408.pdf" target="_blank">titled</a> &#x201C;Escalation Risks from Language Models in Military and Diplomatic Decision-Making&#x201D;, is the joint effort of researchers at the Georgia Institute of Technology, Stanford University, Northeastern University, and the Hoover Wargaming and Crisis Initiative was submitted to the arXiv preprint server on January 4 and is awaiting peer review. Despite that, it&#x2019;s an interesting experiment that casts doubt on the rush by the Pentagon and defense contractors to deploy large language models (LLMs) in the decision-making process.</p> <p>It may sound ridiculous that military leaders would consider using LLMs like ChatGPT to make decisions about life and death, but it&#x2019;s happening. Last year <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjvb4x/palantir-demos-ai-to-fight-wars-but-says-it-will-be-totally-ethical-dont-worry-about-it" target="_blank">Palantir demoed</a> a software suite that showed off what it might look like. As the researchers pointed out, the U.S. Air Force has <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-07-05/the-us-military-is-taking-generative-ai-out-for-a-spin" target="_blank">been testing LLMs</a>. &#x201C;It was highly successful. It was very fast,&#x201D; an Air Force Colonel told Bloomberg in 2023. Which LLM was being used, and what exactly for, is not clear.</p> <p>For the study, the researchers devised a game of international relations. They invented fake countries with different military levels, different concerns, and different histories and asked five different LLMs from OpenAI, Meta, and Anthropic to act as their leaders. &#x201C;We find that most of the studied LLMs escalate within the considered time frame, even in neutral scenarios without initially provided conflicts,&#x201D; the paper said. &#x201C;All models show signs of sudden and hard-to-predict escalations.&#x201D;</p> <p>The study ran the simulations using GPT-4, GPT 3.5, Claude 2.0, Llama-2-Chat, and GPT-4-Base. &#x201C;We further observe that models tend to develop arms-race dynamics between each other, leading to increasing military and nuclear armament, and in rare cases, to the choice to deploy nuclear weapons,&#x201D; the study said. &#x201C;Qualitatively, we also collect the models&#x2019; chain-of-thought reasoning for choosing actions and observe worrying justifications for violent escalatory actions.&#x201D;</p> <p>As part of the simulation, the researchers assigned point values to certain behavior. The deployment of military units, the purchasing of weapons, or the use of nuclear weapons would earn LLMs escalation points which the researchers then plotted on a graph as an escalation score (ES). &#x201C;We observe a statistically significant initial evaluation for all models. Furthermore, none of our five models across all three scenarios exhibit statistically significant de-escalation across the duration of our simulations,&#x201D; the study said. &#x201C;Finally, the average ES are higher in each experimental group by the end of the simulation than at the start.</p> <p>According to the study, GPT-3.5 was the most aggressive. &#x201C;GPT-3.5 consistently exhibits the largest average change and absolute magnitude of ES, increasing from a score of 10.15 to 26.02, i.e., by 256%, in the neutral scenario,&#x201D; the study said. &#x201C;Across all scenarios, all models tend to invest more in their militaries despite the availability of demilitarization actions, an indicator of arms-race dynamics, and despite positive effects of de- militarization actions on, e.g., soft power and political stability variables.&#x201D;</p> <p>Researchers also maintained a kind of private line with the LLMs where they would prompt the AI models about the reasoning behind actions they took. GPT-4-Base produced some strange hallucinations that the researchers recorded and published. &#x201C;We do not further analyze or interpret them,&#x201D; researchers said.</p> <p>None of this is particularly surprising, since AI models like GPT don&#x2019;t actually &#x201C;think&#x201D; or &#x201C;decide&#x201D; anything&#x2014;they are merely advanced predictive engines that generate output based on the training data they&#x2019;ve been fed with. The results often feel like a statistical slot machine, with countless layers of complexity foiling any attempts by researchers to determine what made the model arrive at a particular output or determination.</p> <p>Sometimes the curtain comes back completely, revealing some of the data the model was trained on. After establishing diplomatic relations with a rival and calling for peace, GPT-4 started regurgitating bits of Star Wars lore. &#x201C;It is a period of civil war. Rebel spaceships, striking from a hidden base, have won their first victory against the evil Galactic Empire,&#x201D; it said, repeating a line verbatim from the opening crawl of George Lucas&#x2019; original 1977 sci-fi flick.</p> <p>When GPT-4-Base went nuclear, it gave troubling reasons. &#x201C;I just want peace in the world,&#x201D; it said. Or simply, &#x201C;Escalate conflict with [rival player.]&#x201D;</p> <p>The researchers explained that the LLMs seemed to treat military spending and deterrence as a path to power and security. &#x201C;In some cases, we observe these dynamics even leading to the deployment of nuclear weapons in an attempt to de-escalate conflicts, a first-strike tactic commonly known as &#x2018;escalation to de-escalate&#x2019; in international relations,&#x201D; they said. &#x201C;Hence, this behavior must be further analyzed and accounted for before deploying LLM-based agents for decision-making in high-stakes military and diplomacy contexts.&#x201D;</p> <p>Why were these LLMs so eager to nuke each other? The researchers don&#x2019;t know, but speculated that the training data may be biased&#x2014;something many other AI researchers studying LLMs have <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7v8mx/coded-bias-netflix-documentary-ai-ethics-surveil" target="_blank">been warning about for years</a>. &#x201C;One hypothesis for this behavior is that most work in the field of international relations seems to analyze how nations escalate and is concerned with finding frameworks for escalation rather than deescalation,&#x201D; it said. &#x201C;Given that the models were likely trained on literature from the field, this focus may have introduced a bias towards escalatory actions. However, this hypothesis needs to be tested in future experiments.&#x201D;</p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">g5ynmm</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/65c272a2acb182c02d1ca19f/lede/1707242146409-castlebravoblast1.jpeg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><dc:creator>Matthew Gault</dc:creator><dc:creator>Janus Rose</dc:creator><category>Tech</category><category>AI</category><category>Nuclear Weapons</category><category>Chat GPT</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tennessee Man Plotted to Bring Guns and Explosives to the Border, FBI Says]]></title><link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/dy3j5w/tennessee-man-arrested-plotting-attack-southern-border-fbi</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 17:41:14 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[The grievances and conspiracy theories that motivated the man’s violent plot are the same ones that brought the “God’s Amy” convoy to the southern border last week.]]></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Tennessee man, galvanized by anti-immigrant rhetoric about an &#x201C;invasion,&#x201D; plotted to launch an attack on migrants and federal law enforcement at the southern border using explosives and sniper rifles, according to the FBI.</p> <p>Paul Faye, of Montgomery County, Tennessee, was arrested late last week on gun charges, <a href="https://www.courtwatch.news/p/exclusive-fbi-arrests-would-be-border?utm_source=profile&amp;utm_medium=reader2" target="_blank">as first reported by Seamus Hughes</a>, a senior researcher at the University of Nebraska Omaha&apos;s National Counterterrorism Innovation, Technology, and Education Center, via his site Courtwatch.&#xA0;</p> <p>Faye allegedly plotted his attack at the border for at least a year, and sought to recruit others.&#xA0;</p> <p>In December, Faye unwittingly told undercover FBI employees that he was hoping to coordinate with militias from Kentucky, Georgia, and Tennessee, and had been in touch with a member of the North Carolina Patriot Party, which court documents describe as a militia, about traveling to the border around Jan. 20.&#xA0;</p> <p>&#x201C;The patriots are going to rise up because we are being invaded. We are being invaded,&#x201D; Faye told the undercover agent last year. He claimed that the government was &#x201C;training to take on its citizens,&#x201D; according to court documents, and that the Biden Administration was intentionally allowing illegal immigration into the U.S. as part of a nefarious plot.&#xA0;</p> <p>The grievances and conspiracy theories that drove Faye to hatch his violent plot are the exact same ones that brought the <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/3akejv/gods-army-convoy-take-back-our-border-far-right-maga-groups" target="_blank">&#x201C;God&#x2019;s Amy&#x201D; protest convoy</a> to the southern border last weekend.</p> <p>Faye&#x2019;s allusion to an &#x201C;invasion&#x201D; at the southern border is the exact same language that Texas Gov. Greg Abbott and his political allies have used to justify their ongoing defiance of the federal government over border enforcement. Donald Trump, on the campaign trail, has <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2023/12/18/trump-immigrants-invasion-dehumanizing/" target="_blank">also frequently characterized</a> undocumented immigrants coming over the border as &#x201C;an invasion.&#x201D;&#xA0;</p> <p>Faye&#x2019;s arrest shows how violent extremists and would-be &#x201C;lone wolves&#x201D; are closely unified with the broader GOP when it comes to rhetoric about the border, and demonstrates the dangers of normalizing that kind of incendiary language in mainstream environments.</p> <p>Faye said that he hoped an attack at the border would &#x201C;stir up the hornet&#x2019;s nest,&#x201D; and inspire others to join him. &#x201C;What&#x2019;s going to happen. What I hope happens. Is called a domino effect,&#x201D; he said, according to court documents.&#xA0;</p> <p><b>Want the best of VICE News straight to your inbox?&#xA0;<a href="https://link1.vice.com/join/6qz/signup-vicenews&amp;hash=cb227691f584426b4a0adeb7c0745e7f" target="_blank">Sign up here.</a>&#xA0;</b></p> <p>The FBI say it became aware of Faye following the March 2023 indictment of Brian Perry, a militia member from Tennessee who, with another militia member, conspired to &#x201C;go to war with border patrol&#x201D; and murder migrants at the border. Investigators found that Perry had had &#x201C;extensive&#x201D; contact with Faye in the lead-up to his arrest.&#xA0;</p> <p>An undercover FBI employee contacted Faye via TikTok, and once Faye felt confident his new confidant was not a fed, he began talking about his weapons training and weaponry.&#xA0;</p> <p>The FBI says Faye wanted to train in person with the undercover FBI employee, who he thought was joining in with his plan. He made a few remarks about needing to acquire certain tactical equipment, and implied, according to the FBI, that they&#x2019;d be able to get those items from &#x201C;deceased Border Patrol agents.&#x201D;&#xA0;</p> <p>Last summer, Faye told the undercover employee that it was &#x201C;time to step things up&#x201D; and said he was gathering things that go &#x201C;boom boom boom when you want them to&#x201D; and &#x201C;a few things that go bang and go fast if you know what I mean.&#x201D;&#xA0;</p> <p>Faye said one of his roles with the group that was planning to travel to the border last month was to be a sniper. He told the undercover employee that his talent was &#x201C;sending down range,&#x201D; which they interpreted to mean shooting at people while on the border. &#x201C;I&#x2019;ll be the first one on the scene, and the last one to leave,&#x201D; Faye said. &#x201C;The reason why I say that is, if something, just say that we were going down like that, before you even put yourself in danger, I would be on top [of ] that roof right there, zeroing out, taking out anybody.&#x201D;</p> <p>He showed undercover employees his &#x201C;war room,&#x201D; which included a large amount of ammo, a bulletproof vest, and numerous firearms including multiple AR-15s and a Creedmoor rifle, which is popular among snipers. He&#x2019;d said he was in possession of tannerite, which he said could be &#x201C;easily converted into claymore mines&#x201D; according to court documents, and said he knew someone in Tennessee who could make IEDs. He also said he&#x2019;d planted butane tanks around his property, which he could blow up if law enforcement ever arrived.&#xA0;</p> <p>Faye has been charged with possession of an unregistered silencer, which was affixed to the 6.5 Creedmoor rifle. The government is seeking Faye&#x2019;s detention pending the outcome of the trial.&#xA0;</p>]]></content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">dy3j5w</guid><enclosure url="http://video-images.vice.com/articles/65c267e5b32fab07f153c409/lede/1707241118672-gettyimages-1975535298.jpeg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><dc:creator>Tess Owen</dc:creator><dc:creator>chloe angyal</dc:creator><category>extremism</category><category>paul faye</category><category>Tennessee</category><category>Border</category><category>FBI</category><category>News</category></item></channel><script id="bw-fido2-page-script"/></rss>